{
    "subject": "resource/Phil_Urso",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "American musician, tenor saxophone",
    "human_readable": "Phil Urso is an American musician who plays the tenor saxophone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9136084318161011,
            "question": "Is Phil Urso a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8703305721282959,
            "question": "What type of saxophone does Phil Urso play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7661892771720886,
            "question": "What instrument does Phil Urso play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5983370542526245,
            "question": "What musical genre is Phil Urso associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5341017246246338,
            "question": "What nationality is Phil Urso?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46916696429252625,
            "question": "Where is Phil Urso from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35622721910476685,
            "question": "Are there any notable collaborations Phil Urso has been a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34833383560180664,
            "question": "What is Phil Urso's most famous song or composition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2657547891139984,
            "question": "Does Phil Urso perform live concerts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2612690031528473,
            "question": "Has Phil Urso released any albums or recordings?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Phil Urso is an American musician who plays the tenor saxophone.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1914_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Phil Urso perform live concerts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1914_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Phil Urso's most famous song or composition?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1914_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable collaborations Phil Urso has been a part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1914_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1914_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as all four files mention Phil Urso as a jazz tenor saxophonist, and two of them specifically state that he is American."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Phil Urso being a jazz tenor saxophonist, which supports the statement that he is an American musician who plays the tenor saxophone."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}